Finding Aid for the Horace Tapscott Papers PASC-M.0237
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Music Manuscripts, Series 2.
  - Impressions of the Ghetto (Box 54)
  - Impressions, In and Out (Box 54)
  - In Times Like These (Box 38)
    Score and lead sheet.
  - Inspirations of Silence (Box 55)
  - Isle of Celia (Box 55)
  - Isle of Celia (Box 55)
    "D6 Score"
  - I Wish You Love, 18p. (Box 62)
  - Jessica (Box 55)
  - The Jitterbug Waltz (Box 55)
  - Jo Annette (Box 55)
  - Jonathan, 1 p. (Box 55)
  - Jordu (Box 55)
  - Juba (Box 55)
  - Jungle Juice (Box 55)
  - Khartoun (Box 55)
  - Kinji's Dance (Box 55)
  - Kugichagulia (Box 55)
    Lead sheet and several copies.
  - La Negritude (Box 40)
    Parts for Tenor, Trombone, Piano, and Drums.
  - Laeff (Where Ever You May Be), 14p. (Box 56)
    12 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Lately's Solo (Lester Robertson's solo on "Milestones" with the Gerald Wilson Orchestra) (Box 40)
    Piano score and parts for Alto, Baritone Sax, and Trombone.
  - Lazy Afternoon, 9p. (Box 56)
  - Lenita's Song, 14p. (Box 56)
    13 ensemble parts for various instruments, including 2 parts for voice.
    Lyrics.
  - Leroy Brooks, 20p. (Box 56)
  - Les (Lester), 7p. (Box 56)
    Score and 5 ensemble parts for various instruments. Also, a sheet of chord changes for Dolphy composition "Miss Ann."
  - Libra, 6p. (Box 56)
  - Lift Every Voice (Box 56)
    Score and copies.
  - Like Being In Love (Box 40)
  - Like Eric (Box 56)
  - Like Love (Box 56)
  - Lino's Pad (Box 56)
  - Lino's Pad (Box 69)
    Score, individual ensemble parts, and duplicates.
  - Linda Hill lead sheets, songs, and scores (Box 65)
    Adele -- Autumn of My Soul -- Horace (Pt. 2) Oriental Mama -- If I Didn't Feel All Alone -- I'll Wait And Pray -- Love Song -- Love's Vein -- O ZiLuai (Rain Song) -- Pepper's Tune -- Stretch -- Water Hole Song
  - Listen .. My Children (Box 56)
    Score and ensemble parts for various instruments, and copies.
  - Little Niles (Box 38)
    Incomplete score and 4th Tenor Sax part.
  - Little Girl Blue (Box 40)
  - Litha (Box 56)
  - Little Africa (Box 56)
  - Little A's Chant (Box 56)
  - Little Niles (Box 56)
  - Little Nine to Fiver (Box 63)
  - Little Birds (Box 65)
    Bound lead sheets
  - Little Birds (Box 65)
    Bound lead sheet.
  - Living Room (Box 38)
  - Loneliness (Box 38)
    Lyrics, lead sheet and ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Lonesome Lover (Box 40)
    Partial score and parts for Trumpet and Trombone.
  - Love Me Or Leave Me (Box 40)
  - Love On the Sudan (Box 63)
    Ensemble parts for Harp and Guitar.
  - Lucumi Woman (Box 56)
    Ensmeble parts for various instruments.
  - Luhumba (Box 56)
  - Lush Life (Box 38)
  - Lush Life (Box 56)
  - Lyrics (Box 28)
    The Dark Tree -- Today I Held You -- Little Butterfly -- Fonky Honkies -- Inbetween Niggah -- Escape -- Reach For Your Star -- Walk Together Children -- Pic Nic Day -- No Need To Worry -- Uncle Sam -- Child Of Anger -- Little Reflection -- Not At All -- Dem Folks -- Little Africa -- Effie -- Mothership -- Stacy -- Little Africa -- L'Mumba -- Yo' Child -- Close To Freedom -- Fell The Rhythm -- Praise Him -- World Peace, With Or Without People -- Sandy And Niles -- Leroy Brooks Jr. -- Isle Of Celia -- Effie -- The Giant Has Awakened -- Pearl -- Ballad For Samuel -- Naija's Theme --
  - Macrame (Box 40)
  - Macrame, 2 p. (Box 57)
  - Maestro's Medley (Box 57)
  - Man From Tanganyika, 2 p. (Box 57)
  - Many Nights Ago (Box 57)
    Includes many copies of individual parts.
  - Many Nights Ago (Box 63)
    Copies of ensemble parts for various instruments
  - A Manx Overture - The Isles of Mountains and Glens (Box 65)
    Full score and Flute & Piccolo parts, Bb Trumpet parts, and an incomplete clarinet Part.
  - Mary On Sunday (Box 38)
    Score, piano score, and ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Masters at Work (Box 57)
  - Maude's Moods (Box 40)
  - Maui (Box 57)
  - Medley, 8 p.
    Medley (Composition Master)
  - Medley (Box 40)
    Ensemble parts for various instruments. Titles in medley include: Diane -- Charmaine -- Again -- Blue Heaven -- White Cliffs --
  - The Meeting (Box 57)
  - Michael
  - Mike's Tune, 2 p. (Box 57)
  - Miscellaneous, 39 p. (Box 57)
    Score, arranged by "Act" and "Scene." Pieces/titles include: Chant to the Gods, Prayer of Acceptance, In the Bottom of the Boat, Memba Me, In Da Massa's House, More Than Freddom, Stand Up, Double Paranoia, Child of God, A Black Man's World, Non-Violent Man, Dream On, Third Arm, The Party Song, Black Musical - When Black Folks Party, Why Don't You Feel Free, The Argument, The Muslim Song, 23rd Psalm, Krishna K K, Today 1999, Answers and Questions, Suite Spiritual, What A Friend.
    Composers include Horace Tapscott and Bob Mandolph
  - Miscellaneous (Box 65)
    Parts of compositions and written notes.
  - Mixed, titled, incomplete scores and ensemble parts for various instruments (Box 64)
    Close To You -- Dance Of The Little Children -- Egypt -- Fela Fela -- Fergit It Baby -- Hear My Body Pray -- Can't Make Up Me Mind -- Better Town -- It's All In How You Do It -- Lord Amongst Us -- Lost Children Of The Nile -- Lover Man -- Met My Lord -- More + More -- Maonin' -- My Princess Will Cum -- Out Look -- Time -- The Panther -- Rainy Day -- Signal For Intention -- Somebody's Knocking -- So Many Times -- New Jeffersonville -- Somethin' Wrong -- Subtle Music -- Watch What Happens -- You Take My Love For Granted -- BiBi MKua
  - Mixed, untitled, individual ensemble parts for various instruments (Box 64)
    Unidentified, individual parts, separated from the rest of the piece.
  - Mixed, untitled, lead sheets and songs (Box 64)
    Miscellaneous pages of music, many incomplete.
  - Mixed, titled, ensemble parts for various instruments (Box 65)
    Aneefa -- Un Jour Vis un Foulon -- Whatever It Takes -- Tour De Force (with "Lover Man" on the back) -- Throw Down -- Straight Street -- Social Call -- Shakti -- No Name Bar -- No Deposit, No Return -- The Mystery Song / Ellington -- Muerte (with "Aim" on the back) -- A Mood For Jane -- Messages -- M. M. Blues -- Medley / S. Graham (with "Blues In My Heart" on the back) -- Man For T. -- Little Sunflower -- Little Girl Blue -- Jubilate Deo / G. Gabrieli -- Elaborations -- Divine People -- Desafinado and Summertime -- Cosmos Ark (with "Thom Thum" on the back) -- Chelsea Bride -- Can't Help Lovin' Dat MAn (with "If I Love Again" on the back) -- Blue Lights -- But Beautiful (with "El Gaucho" on the back) -- Black Is Beautiful -- Black In A White World -- Beautiful Love -- Baby Blue -- Afternoon In Paree / John Lewis -- Precious Lord
  - Mixed, titled, incomplete scores (Box 67)
  - The Monk On The Hill, 1 p. (Box 57)
    Piano chart.
  - Moon Rays (Box 57)
  - Most Beneficent, Most Merciful (Box 57)
  - Mother Ship (Be There) (Box 57)
    Score #1 and score #2.
  - My Flavor Is Vanilla (Box 57)
  - My Soul Speaks (Box 57)
  - Mykoseky's 1st Fifth, 1 p. (Box 57)
  - Naima (Box 58)
  - Nakatini Suite (Box 58)
    Score and 6 ensemble parts for various instruments. One part unfinished; ensemble parts incomplete.
  - Nakatini Suite (string version) (Box 58)
    Score for strings and 8 ensemble parts for various instruments. Also a piano part or reduced score.
  - Nature's Wish (Box 58)
    14 ensemble parts for various instruments. No score.
  - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1 p. (Box 40)
    Part for Baritone Sax.
  - The New Day (Box 58)
    22 ensemble parts for various instruments. No score.
  - No. I (Box 40)
    Parts for Flute, Soprano, and Britone Saxophone.
  - Nothing But The Blues, 2p. (Box 58)
  - Nyja's Theme (Box 39)
    Ensemble parts for various istruments.
  - O Happy Day (Opening Theme - Edwin Hawkins Show) (Box 58)
  - Obatala, 3p. (Box 62)
  - Ode to Billie Joe, 2p. (Box 58)
    Score for 11 saxes and rhythm.
  - Of God's Wrath Came The Great Earthquake, 9p. (Box 58)
    9 ensemble parts for various instruments. No score.
  - Ol' Man River (Box 40)
    Sheet music, partial score, and ensemble parts for various instruments
  - On The Nile (Box 58)
    Score and 11 ensemble parts.
  - One For Lately (Box 40)
  - One For O. Double Ya (Box 58)
    Score and 10 various ensemble parts.
  - Oriental Flower, 2 p. (Box 58)
  - P.M. (Box 40)
    Parts for Alto and Trombone.
  - P.A.P.A.(Pan African People's Arkestra), 9 p. (Box 58)
  - P.C.O.P., 5 p. (Box 58)
  - Pearl (Box 58)
    Score (and copy of score) plus 2 sets of 13 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Pearl (concert version), 7 p. (Box 58)
  - People Like Us (Box 59)
    Score, 6 ensemble parts for various instruments, and lyrics.
  - People (Box 63)
    Piano part
    Chords only
  - Peyote Song III (Box 59)
  - Piano parts and piano scores (Box 65)
    The Blessed One -- Blue Glass / Osca Brown -- Lamento di Tristano -- Don't Go To Strangers -- For Horace -- Kaleem -- Let The Spirit Lead -- The New Day -- Plea For The Preacher -- Proud Mary -- Will's Deal -- A Waltz For A Tabby Cat
  - Pine Apple Rag (Box 63)
  - Poem For The Arkestra (Box 59)
  - Prance Dance, 14 p. (Box 59)
    13 ensemble parts for various instruments and 1 lead sheet.
  - Prince (Box 40)
  - Pula Semenya (Box 59)
  - Pulse Of The Mind (Box 59)
  - Quagmyer - 5 A.M. (Box 59)
    Title also given as Quagmeyer at 5 AM.
  - Quest for Peace, 23 p. (Box 59)
  - Restless Nights, 1 p. (Box 62)
    Incomplete trombone part.
  - 'Round Midnite (Box 59)
    Partial score and partial piano part.
  - Ruzadan's Residence (Box 59)
    Tenor part and copies.
  - Sandy & Niles, 5 p. (Box 59)
  - Save The Dance, 2 p. (Box 59)
    Partial ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Sea Wife, 4 p. (Box 59)
  - Selected compositions by Kaeef (Box 63)
    Titles include: "Coltrane's Train," "Encouragements," "High Way Flyers," "Kashaud," "Night Flight," and "New Horizons."
  - Selected Compositions by Oscar Brown Jr. (Box 63)
    Titles include: "Shadows," and "Composition Time."
  - Selected Lead Sheets (Box 63)
    Lead sheets
    Titles include: "Baba teh Avatar," "Vanita's Song," and an unknown title.
  - Selected Lead Sheets (Box 63)
    Sheet music
    Song titles include: "Today A Spark, Tomorrow A Flame," and "We're Moving Toward Our Goal - Mission Impossible."
  - Selected Lead Sheets (Box 63)
    Titles include: "One Time," "Take it Away," and "The Panther."
  - Selected Lead Sheets (Box 63)
    Titles include: "Beautiful Queen of the Sun," "Fly To Your Heart (Till It Sings A Song For You)," "The Greater Side of the Greatest," "Jamillah, My Love," "Peace, Love, You and Me," and "Pyramid of Love."
  - Selected Lead Sheets (Box 63)
    Lead Sheets
    Titles include: "A Prayer for Liliane," "Goodies for the Goodies," "Moon in Aquarius," "Peace of Mind," and "Pandora's Box."
  - Selected Lead Sheets (Box 63)
    Lead sheets for piano - no melodies, chords only.
    Titles include: "Don't Get Around Much Anymore," "It Don't Mean A Thing (If It Ain't Got That Swing)," "love You Madly," "Mood Indigo," and "Sophisticated Lady."
  - Selected Lead Sheets By Abdul-Khaliq Fuasi, 23p. (Box 62)
    Lead Sheets for Bird's Vamp, Chariot, Countless Hours, First Steps, Free As A Bird, I Wish It Could Be Me, Pied Piper, Pushcart, Swept Away, This Love Of Ours, Til It Hurts, Under The Sun, Wing Tips.
  - Selected Lead Sheets by Herbert Baker., 3p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for Capricorn, J.O.B.
  - Selected Lead Sheets By Gary Bias, 4p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for East 101, Theme For Horace T.
  - Selected Lead Sheets By S. Browne, 16p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for Be Cool, Bijou, Blue Grotto, I'm Keeping This Evil Eye On You, Jefferson Hymn, There's A Chill In The Air.
  - Selected lead sheets by Tadd Dameron., 17 p.
    Lead sheets for Beautifully Adorned, Bevah Beeps, A Blue Time, Dial "B" for Beauty, Gnid, Jahbero, Lament For The Living, Mating Call, Milt's Delight, Romas, Sando Latino, Slightly Flighty, Soultrane, Tadd's Delight, Theme Of No Repeat.
  - Selected Lead Sheets By "Guido" Sinclair Greenwell, 10p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for Beautiful, Ghetto School (composed by Sinclair Greenwell and Jo Washington), One For Duke, Pensantradink (composed by Sinclair Greenwell and Jo Washington, Porter In & Out, Up Jumped One (composed by 'Guido' Sinclair Greenwell and Jo Washington. Also, folder contains an untitled sheet and another sheet that may be titled To Dinky Avec L'Amour.
  - Selected Lead Sheets By Sadik Hakim, 12p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for Say What You Mean, Thinking Of Her, Waltz With Me, Why So, Witches Goblins & Etc..
  - Selected Lead Sheets By Clifford Jordan, 2p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for Hot Water, A Story Tale.
  - Selected Lead Sheets By Steve Lacy., 3p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for Esteem, Theme for Ernie.
  - Selected Lead Sheets by Steven Meeks., 4p. (Box 62)
    Selected lead sheets for Mosin' Along, Of Lately.
  - Selected Lead Sheets By Roberto Miranda, 18p. (Box 62)
    At Peace With The Monk, Blue Fog, Deborah Tasmin, Horacio--Horace, Platform For Freedom, Playtude #1 (dedicated to Bobby Bradford),Prayer #1 (for Voice and Piano), The Spirit Of The Dream.
  - Selected Lead Sheets By Wayne Peet and Buddy Toscano, 13p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for The Alchemy Of Bobby Bradford, Child Like Love, Cold Woman, Kathy's Song, Lonely Towns, Love's Never Ending Smile, Magnet & Mirror, Why.
  - Selected lead sheets by Nelly Pouget, 8p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for Bebe Ange, Les Poissons.
  - Selected Lead Sheets By Walter Savage, 4p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for Thai Forest, Women/Tickets.
    Thai Forest lead sheet also contains music for Maude's Moods by Horace Tapscott.
  - Selected Lead Sheets By Michael Sessions, 4p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for No Cash, Short Stop, Unknown, World Class.
  - Selected Lead Sheets By Louie Spears, 5p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets for Twilight, Whit, Wobblin.
  - She's Gone, 2 p.
    Score and lyrics.
  - Sheet music, songs, and lead sheets. (Box 28)
    After Today (from "Doctor Doolittle") -- Allegro de Concert (Saxophone Quartet) / J.B. Singelee -- Almost Next / R. Willis -- Along Came Betty -- Ana Maria / Wayne Shorter -- Angels Flying Through Barbed Wire -- Ans / Arthur Davis -- Art (text by Herman Melville) -- Baha'v'llah -- Beyond Earthly Means -- Black & Tan Fantasy / Ellington-Miley -- Blues For The Season / Art Davis -- Bone / Steve Lacy (text trans. from Lao-Tzu) -- The Brush-Off / Art Dedrick -- Catalonian Christmas Carol -- Celia (Bud Powell transcription) -- Comin' On (w/ "Ashes" on bottom half of page) -- Concerto in D Major, op. 27 - Allegro moderato / Luigi Boccherini -- Dear Old Stockholm -- The Early Dawn / J.F.H. (w/ "The Healer" on the bottom half of page) -- Everybody's Doing It / Art Davis -- Every Time We Say Goodbye -- Fanfare and Alleluia / Merrill Knighton -- Felix Caper No 30 / C. Hobbs (w/ Z Dance(with words) on bottom half of page) -- Free Cell Block F - 'Tis Nazi USA / Mingus -- Fiddler On the Roof -- For Hor Us -- God Bless' The Child -- Gone With The Wind -- Goodbye / Gordon Jenkins -- Happiness / Roy Porter -- Happy Free and Easy -- Hart Thought - A Song of Truth / T.L. Tedesco (dedicated to Roberto Miranda) -- Hear the Lambs A-Cryin -- A Hole In One -- How Long Has This Been Going On? -- I'll Remember April -- The Impossible Dream (from Man of La Mancha) -- Isotope / Joe Henderson -- Journey Into Nigritia / N. Morgan -- Laura / D. Raskin -- Latin Escapade -- Listen to the Dawn / K. Burrell -- Little Boy, Why Are You Crying -- Lover Man -- Love's Never Ending Smile (page 2) -- Mother -- Nigeria / Frances Benda -- Pan Con Queso / Joe Loco -- Paradox -- Passion Flower -- Peter Tworsky -- Play Daddie Play -- Portrait of Cousin Mickey -- Re-Incarnation of A Love Bird / Mingus -- Rahsaan's Return -- Remembering / K. Burrell -- Right Out That Window -- Searchin' for Freedom - Part One / James Newton & Jon Jang -- The Star-Crossed Lovers / Ellington & Strayhorn -- A Time Remembered -- Skylark -- Smooth As The Wind / Tadd Dameron -- Soul Eyes (w/ "The Sweetest Sounds" on bottom half of page) -- Sunny / Bobby Hebb -- That One / Art Davis -- Time For Dreams / Roy Porter -- Touch Of Love -- Turnaround / Ornette Coleman (w/ "A Call For All Demons" by Sun Ra on bottom half of page) -- Valse Hot / Sonny Rollins -- Why Do I Love You? / Jerome Kern -- Winds / Leon Thomas -- Wise One / Coltrane -- Zo Is Het / V. Vingerhoeds
  - She's Gone, 2p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets and lyrics.
  - Sketches of Drunken Mary (Box 59)
    Partial score and 12 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Sketches of Inez, 16 p. (Box 59)
    9 partial ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Something For Kenny, 5 p. (Box 59)
    Score and bass part.
  - Song of the Caterpillar (Box 39)
  - Sonny's Dream (Box 39)
    Score on onion paper, and ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Song for Shawisi (Box 59)
  - Song to the Ancestors (Box 63)
    Incomplete ensemble parts.
    Parts for Tuba and Alto Saxophone.
  - Songs and Lead Sheets (Box 65)
    Blues For Yna Yna / Gerald Wilson and Teddy Edwards -- Carnival -- Everything Costs Sompin / Foster Johnson -- Femme Fatale / Bobby West -- Fire Waltz / Mal Waldron -- The Half Dozens, Hallucinations, and In The Nick Of Time / Bill Holman, Bud Powell, and Milty Gold -- Hey Black Brother / Avotcja Ackerman -- It's No Use Crying -- It's Time -- Keep Your Eye On The Doughnut / Foster Johnson -- Leland's Song -- Livin' In The Ghetto / L. Farrow -- Love Is A Gamble / Joann Bruno and Milton DeShone -- Love Thy Neighbor -- Miss Ann / Eric Dolphy -- Love Child / Foster Johnson -- Moment's Notice / John Coltrane -- Moon Rays -- My Foolish Heart / Washington and Young -- O What A Beautiful Day / NiRuma -- On A Clear Day / Burton Lane -- One For Joan / Charles Lloyd -- Party Tonite / Roy and Tina Porter -- Please Don't Talk About Me When I'm Gone -- Shadows -- Spellbound / Cliff Jordan -- Sunrise Sunset -- Uccioimi Dolore / Jacopo Peri -- We've Got It Made / Sam Theard and Ernestine McClendon -- The Wise Ones -- You Give Me (Sweet Music) / Larry Farrow
  - Songs And Dances Of The Inner Self (Incarnate Dance), 14 p. (Box 59)
  - Sonny's Dream, 18 p. (Box 59)
    Score is titled Sonny's Dream Version II and dated 5/2/77.
  - Spirit (II-1), 1 p. (Box 39)
  - The Spider (Box 59)
  - Spirituals (miscellaneous), 14 p. (Box 62)
    Music and lyrics for 4 bound compositions. I See Him by Janie Cawthron,lyrics by Kenneth Morris; You Can't Make It Alone (music and lyrics by Janie Cawthron); Two Darkey Songs (collected and arranged by David Guion; Negro Spirituals (arranged for solo voice by H.T. Burleigh).
  - Stacy, 5p. (Box 62)
    Score for voice and keyboard.
  - Stolen Moments, 13 p. (Box 59)
  - Submissive Woman (Box 60)
    Partial score and ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Suite Spirituals (Box 39)
  - Suite, 70 p. (Box 60)
  - Sunny Gets Blue, La Rene La Rue (Clairsie Daniel) (Box 40)
  - Sunrise At Midnight, 6 p. (Box 60)
    Partial score.
  - Sweet Jesus The Preacher Man (motion picture), 1973 (Box 60)
    Score and partial scores.
    Folder includes a score titled "Sweet Jesus," music by Linda Hill; lyrics by Joann Bruno.
  - Take Me Back (Box 60)
  - Tell Me Why, 20 p. (Box 60)
  - That's Where It's At (Box 40)
    Score on onion paper
  - Thank You Jah, Original and photocopies. (Box 60)
    Vocal arrangement and lyric sheet.
  - That Last Note (Box 60)
    Partial conductor's score and 8 partial ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - That's Me, 3 p. (Box 60)
    Song lyrics and music.
  - Theme for Horace T., 1 p. (Box 61)
    Bass part only.
  - Theme for Horace T. (Box 68)
  - Theme For Rhea (Box 61)
    Partial conductor's score and 10 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Theme For Rhea (Box 68)
  - There Ain't No Rules, 12 p. (Box 61)
  - There Ain't No Rules (Box 68)
  - These Are Soulful Days, 10 p. (Box 61)
  - These Are Soulful Days (Box 68)
  - The Thin Line, 14 p. (Box 61)
    Conductor's score.
  - The Thin Line (Box 68)
  - This Is For Benny (Box 61)
    Score for bass, traps, and melodic line.
    Score includes "Niger's Theme" and "Mary on Sunday."
  - This Is For Benny (Box 68)
  - Thoughts Of Dar Es Salaam, 29 pages plus photocopies (Box 61)
    Partial score and 10 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Thoughts Of Dar Es Salaam (Box 68)
  - To The Great House, 7 p. (Box 61)
    Score and partial ensemble parts for tenor sax, percussion, and traps.
  - Tour De Force, 1p. (Box 62)
    Score for drums.
  - Trane Medley (Box 61)
  - Umatu, 4 p. (Box 61)
    3 ensemble parts.
  - Unidentified title (The Gypsy?) (Box 39)
  - UGMAA (Union of Gods' Musicians And Artists Association) (Box 61)
  - Unity (Box 61)
    Score and incomplete ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Unidentified score from a folder labelled, "Helbie Ziroe." (Box 63)
    pages 4 through 22.
  - Unity, 13 p. (Box 61)
  - Unknown Title (Dreams of Mr. Big?; part of Dream Suite?) (Box 39)
    score on onion paper
  - Untombindie - The Dreaming Princess (Box 39)
  - Utopia, 2 p. (Box 61)
  - Lead sheets by Thelonious Monk; Fuasi Abdul-Khaliq., 21p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheets by Thelonius Monk, Fuasi Abdul-Khaliq, and one composition by Roberto Miranda.
  - Various ensemble parts for various compositions (Box 63)
    Titles include: "Allah (A Prayer)," and "Eternal Egypt"
  - Various ensemble parts for various compositions (Box 63)
    Incomplete ensemble parts for various instruments.
    Titles include: "In A Sentimental Mood," "I Got It Bad," "In A Mellow Tone," "Black and Tan Fantasy," "Mood Indigo," and "What Am I Here For."
  - Various Ensemble Parts for various compositions (Box 63)
    Incomplete ensemble parts for varius instruments
    Titles include: "Mt. Zion," and "Hear the Lamb's A-Cryin'"
  - Various Songs (Box 63)
    Sheet music for songs including: "I Can See," "If I Ever Start Crying," "In A Garden," "The Lord Is Among Us," "Miracle," and "Moaning."
  - Vibeke (Box 39)
  - Village Dance, 10 p. (Box 61)
  - The Village Musicians (The Creator's Musicians) (Box 61)
  - Visions Of Another Time, 22 p. (Box 61)
  - The Vulture, 2 p. (Box 61)
  - Warrior's Mate (Box 61)
    Revised score, original score (and copy of original score) and 17 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Warriors All (Box 66)
  - What's New (Box 40)
  - When He Comes (Box 39)
  - Who Are You?, 13 p. (Box 61)
  - Why? (Box 61)
    Score, dated 11-12-66.
  - Why Don't You Listen (Box 61)
  - A Wise Man Will Hear (Box 61)
    Score is from "The Black Carnival."
  - World Peace With or Without People (Box 63)
  - You Are Love (Box 40)
- Miscellaneous, Series 3.
  - [Untitled] (Box 28)
    Unidentified screenplay.
  - Adam In The Morning (Box 28)
    William Marshall screenplay.
  - Enter Frederick Douglass - A One-Man Dramatization (Box 28)
    Transcript of KCET presentation by Willim Marshall.
  - William Marshall Presents Frederick Douglass (Box 28)
    Teleplay by Sylvia Jarrico.